County Deputy.
You are caught in the illusion of Crimson Greed Lycoris.
You will be trapped in your own greed
for the rest of your lives.
Hahaha.
Why does this tree look so familiar?
Greetings, Grandmaster.
Grandmaster?
Me?
Grandmaster.
The demons of the Kui Clan in the West Mountain have been wiped out.
The remaining Flood Dragons of the Rakshasa Sea
are still making moves.
Should we eradicate them as well?
Eradicate them.
The Flood Dragons have been there for a millennium. They are quite powerful.
I wish to take a hundred thousand golden-body disciples
under your command to go.
Please grant your permission.
How many? A hundred thousand?
Do you think it's not enough?
Then a million.
Oh, no.
A hundred thousand is fine. Go.
Grandmaster.
These are the supreme spells we seized
while encircling the Kui Clan.
Please accept this, Grandmaster.
Advanced magic.
Good.
Hahaha.
Hahaha, hahaha.
Gesang.
Why,
Gesang,
don't you want to cultivate with me?
Of course I do.
Illusion.
I wanted to spare your lives.
Since you are government officials,
I didn't want to kill you myself.
However,
since you dared to bring someone to fight me,
don't blame me for not giving you a chance.
Witch!
Kill us if you want.
We failed the people of Er City
by believing your nonsense.
We may not be able to catch you today,
but someone will avenge us.
Fine.
Let's see
who else can save you today.
Break!
What? How could the illusion of Chilan Bi'an
be broken?
Could it be...
you have no greed?
Golden blade shines, breaking through all.
Embrace the origin, shake the universe.
An immortal!
So this is
the Sanshan Sect's
Golden Immortal.
You,
are actually the Liujin Immortal of the Three Mountains!
[Search]
Please.
The betrothal gift is meager, but I hope you will accept it.
I only have this one daughter,
and I worry about having no one to manage the bank.
If you want to marry her,
you must marry into our family.
I will leave the Rui family's business to you.
I will work hard.
Keep up the good work.
Mr. Wang,
we'll really need your help with the bank matter this time.
This business yields a full 20 percent profit.
Look,
we must settle the accounts clearly with them.
What are you all good for?
Regarding this debt,
if I can't collect it,
how will I answer to my father-in-law?
Open it.
Open it!
Take it.
Here, take it.
You're finally here, sir.
Sir.
Drink this cup.
Come on.
Father.
Don't scare me.
Don't leave me.
Come.
Yichen.
What are you doing?
The Way of Heaven is constant.
Everything has a fixed destiny.
Let go of anger and hatred.
Return to the right path.
It is not too late.
Ping Jieqiang Haihui.
Jieqiang Hai.